Then Jolyne got punished on purpose
so that she gets confined
at the Disciplinary Wing to find the bone!
Yes.
If I successfully protect her to the end,
then I will marry her.
This is my condition.
Got that?
Diver Drive!
Give us your blessing.
The electric potential sending
signals to the nervous system
is very small, at 70mV.
This Stand dwells in
that slight pulse of energy.
Survivor's attack is mostly unnoticed,
and it doesn't cause any harm.
It simply awakens its victim's anger.
EPISODE 16: THE SECRET OF GUARD WESTWOOD
Bastards!
I can see
the strongest parts
of each fighter's body from here!
It's Fight Club time!
Let's brawl!
I've always found you irritating, fuckers!
The enemy User must be among them.
One of them manipulated
the guards into fighting.
The bone lurking somewhere within
this Ultra Security House Unit…
I'll do anything it takes to make it mine!
I won't let anyone stand in my way.
If anyone dares, I will kill--
Hold on… kill?
Did I really think that just now?
This burning feeling awakening within me…
Is this my fighting spirit?
It urges me to conquer all
no matter who I'm up against
or what happens to me.
Why do I feel so aggressive?
This prison guard…
Now, he wants to do to me
what he did to the other guard.
But that's fine.
He's no match for my Stone Ocean.
Stone Ocean!
I can see it, FE40536.
I can see your strongest point.
It's the thread-like thing
coming out of your muscles.
It's beautiful.
So that's your strongest power.
His movements just now…
Though his fight with the other guard
was uncanny and brutal,
it was still just a brawl.
But now,
his movements are beyond
what humans can do!
I have to defeat him with all my power
as fast as I can!
The guard's muscles…
They are shining beautifully.
Also, the sequence
of his movements just now…
How is a human capable
of ignoring fear and pain
to exert that much force
when attacking and jumping?
But if the beautiful lights
emanating from his muscles
indicate his strongest parts,
then that leg of his right now…
That's the leg I attacked.
My attack was effective!
I can feel it.
I can tell that my attack
did some deep damage to his leg!
Bastard.
Who said you can walk in front of me?
You're pissing me off!
The others have started fighting too.
Take this!
Damn prison guard!
I must incapacitate him as quickly
as I can and focus on finding the bone!
Good thing you didn't wring your own neck
with that swing of yours.
Now, just stay there!
What the hell just happened?
How did he attack me?
This prison guard!
What did you do just now?
This is…
So he is also a Stand User.
There's more than one User
in this Disciplinary Wing.
He already had a Stand on a disc!
But what did he do, and how?
I left him no chance to counter me.
And I didn't see his Stand,
so how did he attack me?
It's deep.
Fuck, it's deep.
He can't leave a wound this deep
with a stashed razor blade or a knife.
Just what did he do to me?
If he has a power-type Stand,
then I should be able to see it!
FE40536.
You use threads to attack.
I see threads
and a bundle of them in your body.
Your strongest power comes
from using this ability.
That's what makes you strong.
How beautiful.
I can see your shine.
When did you become a Stand User?
Yesterday?
Or a moment ago?
I saw it!
I saw his Stand!
His Stand took form!
A Stand User…
So this bastard is the assassin
sent to eliminate me.
Strings do not require power to defend.
A punch's straight trajectory
can easily be changed
by throwing it off by just a little.
Right into my trap.
Now that you've used both of your arms,
I can restrict all your movements.
In other words…
you'll get covered with my jacket.
Stone Ocean!
I won't let you get back up.
Wha… what?
It's happening again!
What does his Stand do?
No, I can't see it! What did it do?
I have you now!
You're just a piece of shit.
You've made a fool out of me.
How dare you.
Prisoners are the scum of society.
Nothing infuriates me more than
scum like you treating me like shit.
I spent every day on duty
irritated like this.
How dare you look down on me.
I'll make you pay.
I'm not holding back anymore!
I'll release my anger now.
I won't hold anything back.
I'll make sure you pay.
I am the strongest!
I'm going crazy,
and you're going to get it!
What's that on the ceiling window?
No, so his Stand is…
This isn't good!
At this rate, I'll be…
I have to get away!
His Stand's attack is coming towards me!
I got you now.
I've completely locked you in.
Did you forget that I'm a prison guard?
I detain prisoners
almost every day at my job.
Your right hand may seem to be free,
but this headlock does more than choke.
I'm also twisting the joint
on your left shoulder
so that your right arm goes dead
and doesn't rise.
Your right hand won't reach my face.
This headlock has one weakness,
which I know very well.
Your right hand is free to grab my balls.
Of course, I wouldn't mind that
if the situation were different.
But I can even block that too!
It's coming!
If I don't do something,
his Stand's true form will…
That ceiling!
The ceiling window's hard glass…
Those cracks!
I have to break free!
Stone Ocean!
I tore his eardrum!
His grip loosened!
The universe is full of countless
space rocks and debris.
Many of such rocks are drawn in
by the gravitational pull of the earth.
While the majority disintegrate
before reaching the surface,
what if the meteorites
could retain optimal angle and speed
while entering the atmosphere?
STAND NAME: STARLIGHT WAVES
STAND MASTER: VIVANO WESTWOOD
Oh, so you're coming too.
I can do this by myself.
I make and call the shots around here.
Yes, I asked for your help,
but let's make that clear.
Also, if Pale Snake really is determined
to eliminate Jolyne,
he must have sent two assassins,
no, even more than that.
There must be at least
three Stand Users after Jolyne's life.
You and I will get rid of them,
then meet back here.
Got that?
Fine.
I plan to be back
before that guard wakes up.
Also, we already agreed that
I'll marry Jolyne.
Don't forget that.
Yeah, so about that…
What the hell do you mean?
I really don't get you.
Meteorites!
His attacks are the meteorites
that are drawn to this prison guard!
That's what was smashing into me.
His Stand attracts meteorites from space.
But they always
burn away before they can hit him.
And another one will fall.
He'll attract another one!
Before that happens…
I got you!
This time, I won't let go!
I'll be the victor, shining beautifully.
I am the strongest!
Stone Ocean!
I'll strip off your skin from toe to head!
Now let me go, you fucking guard!
He loosened his grip!
I barely dodged them.
I tried to deflect the meteorites
toward him,
but it's just like the last time.
Not a single meteorite will hit him.
They disintegrate the moment
before they hit him!
That prison guard's Stand ability
attracts the falling meteorites
toward his body like a magnet!
But no matter what I try,
the meteorites hit only me
when I get close to him.
How bizarre.
Burning rocks are falling
toward me from the sky.
Are they meteorites?
Could this be my strongest power?
FE40536.
How many of them have smashed into you?
Your wounds look serious.
They got both your arms,
your left ribs, and your right leg.
So that's five times.
Or is that six?
The next one will be your fatal blow.
What a bluff.
You are barely able to stand right now.
Not even, you are just trying
to fool me with that stance.
In truth, you can't fight me
with those arms anymore.
Your arm muscles are pitch-black.
The muscles have really lost their shine.
Why don't we fool around a bit?
Let's see how bad your damage is.
What's the matter?
Come on, give me a swing.
I'm not even blocking.
Here, attack me.
How do you want to punch me?
I'll even close my eyes for you.
Over there!
That little thing he's got.
That's the bone Pale Snake is after!
That's the bone! It's right over there!
You can't even fight anymore!
You are using the wall
to block the meteorites.
I knew you'd try that!
Meteorites were already
crashing towards me
from the other side of the wall!
I won!
I knew it, you are so damaged
that you can't even block my blows!
One stared at the wall
While the other looked up at the stars
On the other side of the bars
Which am I?
And now, one more hit!
The bone is right over there.
I will do anything
to get close to Pale Snake.
I'll even drink sewage water.
I'll even become the strongest!
I win!
There's no way for you
to escape the meteorite now!
Of course, I want to look up at the stars.
I want to keep looking at them
until I see Dad again.
Good grief.
Here comes your final blow!
You're done for!
I can't dodge this final blow.
I can't block it with Stone Ocean anymore.
I am superior!
But…
I did manage to slip off your right shoe.
She even put a brick in my boot!
She took the hit,
but the damage was halved!
She changed its course!
The meteorite will disintegrate.
It's impossible to hit you with it.
I'm strictly speaking about
the meteorite, that is.
My boot!
Seriously, good grief.
You bitch!
Stone Ocean!
What is up with this bitch?
She really doesn't give up.
She doesn't give up at all.
Dammit.
Yes, if the meteorite collides
into something else first,
then she can hit me with it.
How terrible.
How dare she do
such a terrible thing against me.
This woman…
I choose to look up at the stars.
Match over!
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter